<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Eclipse 4diac</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Eclipse 4diac</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3rd 4diac Users&#39; Workshop @ ETFA 2012</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2012/</guid>
      <description>The 3rd Users&amp;rsquo; Workshop has been hold in conjunction with the 17th IEEE International Conference on Emerging Technologies and Factory Automation (ETFA) in Kraków.
Workshop Date: 21th September 2012
Workshop Organizers Alois Zoitl, fortiss GmbH, Germany Gerhard Ebenhofer, PROFACTOR GmbH, Austria Thomas Strasser, AIT Austrian Institute of Technology, Austria Workshop Program: Morning Session Welcome and Recent Activities of the 4DIAC Open Source Initiative A. Zoitl (Vienna University of Technology) Integration of IEC 61131-3 and IEC 61499 control logic using FORTE and ProConOS S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4days of 4diac</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/workshops/2019_4days_of_4diac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/workshops/2019_4days_of_4diac/</guid>
      <description>4 days for the 4diac community to meet and exchange!
What is 4days of 4diac? It is a place for bringing 4diac users and contributors together to show, discuss and program with each other on new 4diac topics and applications.
Where will 4days of 4diac take place? LIT Open Innovation Center @ JKU Linz
When are the 4days of 4diac? Start: Nov. 11th 2019, 1pm End: Nov. 14th 2019, 3pm Where to register for 4days of 4diac?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th 4diac Users&#39; Workshop @ ETFA 2013</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2013/</guid>
      <description>The 4th Users&amp;rsquo; Workshop has been hold in conjunction with the 18th IEEE International Conference on Emerging Technologies and Factory Automation (ETFA) in Cagliari, Italy.
Workshop Date: 10th September 2013
Workshop Organizers Alois Zoitl, fortiss GmbH, Germany Gerhard Ebenhofer, PROFACTOR GmbH, Austria Thomas Strasser, AIT Austrian Institute of Technology, Austria Workshop Program: Morning Session Welcome and Recent Activities of the 4DIAC Open Source Initiative G. Ebenhofer (Profactor GmbH), A. Zoitl (fortiss GmbH) Application Experiences Challenges and experiences using 4DIAC for Smart Grid laboratory automation F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th 4diac Users&#39; Workshop @ ETFA 2014</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2014/</guid>
      <description>The 5th Users&amp;rsquo; Workshop has been hold in conjunction with the 19th IEEE International Conference on Emerging Technologies and Factory Automation (ETFA) in Barcelona.
Workshop Date: 16th September 2014
Workshop Organizers Alois Zoitl, fortiss GmbH, Germany Gerhard Ebenhofer, PROFACTOR GmbH, Austria Thomas Strasser, AIT Austrian Institute of Technology, Austria Workshop Program: Morning Session Welcome and Recent Activities of the 4DIAC Open Source Initiative A. Zoitl (fortiss GmbH) Infrastructure Enhancements Extending 4DIAC with a partitioning and scheduling tool M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6th 4diac Users&#39; Workshop @ ETFA 2015</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2015/</guid>
      <description>The 6th Users&amp;rsquo; Workshop is held in conjunction with the 20th IEEE International Conference on Emerging Technologies and Factory Automation (ETFA) in Luxembourg.
Workshop Date: 8th September 2015
Workshop Organizers Alois Zoitl, fortiss GmbH, Germany Gerhard Ebenhofer, PROFACTOR GmbH, Austria Thomas Strasser, AIT Austrian Institute of Technology, Austria Workshop Program: Morning Session Welcome and Recent Activities of the 4DIAC Open Source Initiative A. Zoitl (fortiss GmbH) Using IEC 61499 for Virtual Commissioning Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7th 4diac Users&#39; Workshop @ ETFA 2016</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2016/</guid>
      <description>The 7th Users&amp;rsquo; Workshop is held in conjunction with the 21th IEEE International Conference on Emerging Technologies and Factory Automation (ETFA) in Berlin.
Workshop Date: 6th September 2016
Registration Information: Registration details for the workshop can be found at the ETFA web-page.
Workshop Organizers Alois Zoitl, fortiss GmbH, Germany Gerhard Ebenhofer, PROFACTOR GmbH, Austria Thomas Strasser, AIT Austrian Institute of Technology, Austria Workshop Program: Morning Session Welcome and Recent Activities of the 4DIAC Open Source Initiative A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Insight: Cross Domain Engineering</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/workshops/2019_eclipse_insight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/workshops/2019_eclipse_insight/</guid>
      <description>What is an Eclipse Insight? Like an Eclipse DemoCamp, an Eclipse Insight is a collaborative event featuring technical talks and demonstrations from the Eclipse community. The topic of the event will be more focused on a certain technology area of the Eclipse ecosystem.
Eclipse Insight: Cross Domain Engineering The software amount in all engineering domains is rapidly increasing as well as the complexity of today&amp;rsquo;s software applications. To manage future software systems new engineering methods are required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st 4diac Users&#39; Workshop @ ETFA 2010</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2010/</guid>
      <description>The 1st Users&amp;rsquo; Workshop has been hold in conjunction with the 15th IEEE International Conference on Emerging Technologies and Factory Automation (ETFA) in Bilbao.
Workshop Date: 16th September 2010
Workshop Organizers: Alois Zoitl, Vienna University of Technology, Austria Martijn Rooker, Profactor GmbH, Austria Antonio Valentini, O3neida Europe, Belgium Workshop Program: Morning Session Welcome Antonio Valentini (O3neida Europe) Introduction to 4DIAC Ingo Hegny (Vienna University of Technology) Implementation of Control Systems and Future Trends at the Martin-Luther University using 4DIAC Christian Gerber (Martin-Luther-University) Using FORTE in Infomechatronics lab, The University of Auckland William Dai (University of Auckland Utilizing Lego Mindstorms nxt(tm) as teaching and training platform for IEC 61499 Alois Zoitl (Vienna University of Technology) SIFB Development Approach to Provide Control and Real Time Communication Federico Perez (University of the Basque Country) 4DIAC and wireless sensor networks for factory automation Robert Brennan (University of Calgary) 4DIAC Initiative near future plans Alois Zoitl (Vienna University of Technology, Austria) Open discussion Moderator: Antonio Valentini, O3neida Europe </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd 4diac Users&#39; Workshop @ ETFA 2011</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
        <author>4diac-dev@eclipse.org (Eclipse 4diac Team)</author>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/4diac/events/etfa/etfa2011/</guid>
      <description>The 2nd Users&amp;rsquo; Workshop has been hold in conjunction with the 16th IEEE International Conference on Emerging Technologies and Factory Automation (ETFA) in Toulouse.
Workshop Date: 9th September 2011
Workshop Organizers: Alois Zoitl, fortiss GmbH Antonio Valentini, O3NEIDA Europe Thomas Strasser, AIT Austrian Institute of Technology Workshop Program: Morning Session Welcome Antonio Valentini (O3NEIDA Europe, Belgium) Overview and Update Alois Zoitl (Vienna University of Technology, Austria) Communication Integration New FORTE Communication Infrastructure Michael Hofmann (Profactor GmbH, Austria) EtherNet/IP as communication infrastructure for distributed control applications Alois Zoitl (Vienna University of Technology, Austria) Accessing remote I/Os with Ethernet POWERLINK and 4DIAC Filip Andrén (Austrian Institute of Technology, Austria) SIFB set for accessing Beckhoff controllers using ADS protocol Federico Pérez (Escuele Superior de Ingenieros, Bilbao, Spain) Application Modelling Coordination control of a bin picking application Michael Hofmann (Profactor GmbH, Austria) Supervisory control of an injection molding machine Alois Zoitl (Vienna University of Technology, Austria) 4DIAC for Smart Grids Applications Thomas Strasser (Austrian Institute of Technology, Austria) Plenary Discussion - Future Development of 4diac: Goals and Targets </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>